Guide to the Special events collection ARCH074
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Special events collection
1957-2018
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
University of Hartford
ARCH074
26 Linear Feet (73 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open to all researchers.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of newspaper clippings, press releases, programs, planning documents, photographs, and recordings pertaining to convocations, commencements, and other University hosted events (primarily speakers, lectures, conferences, and other ceremonies) from 1957 to the present. The collection is not exhaustive and information pertaining to events may be found in other collections.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in eight series: I. University Anniversaries, II. Commencement, III. Convocation, IV. Other Events, V. Photographs, VI. Recordings, VII. Artifacts, VIII. Duplicates.
Photographs; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Cultural artifacts; Commencement ceremonies; Speeches, addresses, etc.; Anniversaries; Special events; University of Hartford; University of Hartford -- Anniversaries
- University Anniversaries, 1982-2011; I
  - 25th Anniversary, 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary - All University Weekend (All-U Weekend), 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 2)
  - 25th Anniversary & Library Anniversary Materials, 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 3)
  - 25th Anniversary News Articles and Programs, 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - 25th Anniversary Observer, 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 6)
  - 25th Anniversary Time Capsule, 1982 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 7)
    Scope and Contents
    This file contains information pertaining to the planning and publicity of the 25th Anniversary time capsule. The materials buried in the time capsule can be found in the Artifacts Series.
  - 30th Anniversary, 1986 - 1987 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 8 - 9)
  - 40th Anniversary, 1997; 1 Files One oversize 13 x 18 folder and one legal size folder (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 10, Box Artifacts 5)
    The file consists of mostly local government proclamations to the University of Hartford and a schedule of events.
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Anderson, Mary Daglio, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 11)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Ashton-Pritting, Randi, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 12)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Bacon, Ethel, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 13)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Boothe, Power, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 14)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Calvocoressi, Tom, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 15)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Carson, John, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 16)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Colarulli, Chuck, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 17)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Condon, Charles, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 18)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Cote, Dick (Athletics), 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 19)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Fairfieldsonn, Jim, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 20)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Fitzmaurice, Ann, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 21)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Gort, G., 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 22)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Keener, Jim, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 23)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Lee, Jeneen, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 24)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Lindenauer, Leslie, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 25)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Lindsay, Delois, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 26)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview LoMagilo, A. Peter Athletic Program at Hillyer in Chauncey Harris School, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 27)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Manzione, Lou, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 28)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Meiser-McKnett, Pat Athletics, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 29)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Mitchell, Walter, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 1, Folder 30)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Morrison, Malcolm, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 1)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Scorso, Sharon, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 2)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Silpe, Linda, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 3)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Simmonds, Diana, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 4)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Sorrentino, Sebastion "Sebby", 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 5)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Steinburg, M., 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 6)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Sweitzer, Fred, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 7)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Volker, Joe, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 8)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Weinswig, Ed, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 9)
  - 50th Anniversary Interview Winfree, Glenn, 2006 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 10)
  - 50th Anniversary Events, 2006 - 2007 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 11)
  - 50th Anniversary Miscellaneous, 2006 - 2007 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 12)
  - 50th Anniversary Posters, 2006-2007; 1 Files (Box Shared Oversized 1)
    Poster reads "It's Nifty to Be Fifty!"
  - 50th Anniversary Time Capsule, 2006 - 2007 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 13)
  - 50th Anniversary Spring Kickoff, 2007 Jan 25 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 14)
  - 50th Anniversary Dionne Warwick Concert, 2007 Oct 20 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 15)
  - 50th Anniversary Letters, Proclamations, and Citations, 2007 (Box Artifacts 5)
    The file includes letters written by University President Walt Harrison to the University Community, as well as proclamations, and citations given to the University of Hartford by the state and local governments.
  - 54th Anniversary, 2011 (Box Anniversaries 2, Folder 16)
    This file includes a Facebook photo contest flyer, red birthday cone hats, and several Happy Birthday University of Hartford Buttons.
- Commencement, 1958-2018; II
  - 1958 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 2-3)
    File includes Commencement Honorary Degrees and Baccalaureate (The First U of H) materials.
  - 1959 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 4)
    File includes: Baccalaureate - Commencement - Honorary Degrees - Ball
  - 1960 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 5)
    File includes: Baccalaureate - Commencement
  - 1961 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 6)
  - 1962 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 7)
  - 1963 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 8-9)
  - 1964 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 10-11)
    File includes: Baccalaureate - Commencement - Honorary Degrees and Lee, Percy Maxim - New Head of Pres. Johnson's Consumer Advisory Council.
  - 1965 (Box Commencement 1, Folder 12-13)
    Inlcudes: Baccalaureate - Commencement - Ball
  - 1966 (Box Commencement 2, Folder 1)
    File includes: Baccalaureate - Commencement - Ball
  - 1967 (Box Commencement 2, Folder 2-3)
    File includes: Baccalaureate - Commencement - Honorary Degrees - Ball - Ritual for Conferring Degrees
  - 1968 (Box Commencement 2, Folder 4 - 6)
  - 1969 (Box Commencement 2, Folder 7)
  - 1970 (Box Commencement 2, Folder 8-10)
    File inclcudes: Thomas Broitman, First Student Speaker at a Commencement, and McDermott.
  - 1971 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 1)
  - 1971 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 2-3)
  - 1972 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 4-5)
  - 1973 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 6)
  - 1974 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 7)
  - 1975 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 8)
  - 1976 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 9)
  - 1977 (Box Commencement 3, Folder 10 - 12)
    File Includes Commencement Rituals Materials.
  - 1978 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 1 - 3)
    Files Contain Materials Pertaining Commencement with files specifically related to Media Coverage and Newspaper Articles.
  - 1979 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 4)
  - 1980 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 5)
  - 1981 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 6 - 7)
  - 1982 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 8 - 10)
    Files Contain Materials Pertaining Commencement with files specifically related to Time Capsule and Hirschfeld, Albert.
  - 1983 (Box Commencement 4, Folder 11)
  - 1984 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 1)
  - 1985 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 2)
  - 1986 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 3 - 4)
    Files Contain Materials Pertaining Commencement with files specifically related to Teodor Geisel.
  - 1987 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 5)
  - 1988 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 6 - 7)
    Files Contain Materials Pertaining Commencement with files specifically related to George Burns.
  - 1989 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 8)
  - 1990 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 9)
  - 1991 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 10)
  - 1992 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 11)
  - 1993 (Box Commencement 5, Folder 12)
  - 1994 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 1)
  - 1995 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 2)
  - 1996 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 3)
  - 1997 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 4)
  - 1998 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 5)
  - 1999 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 6)
  - 2000 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 7)
  - 2001 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 8)
  - 2002 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 9)
  - 2003 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 10)
  - 2004 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 11)
  - 2005 (Box Commencement 6, Folder 12)
  - 2006 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 1)
  - 2007 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 2)
  - 2008 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 3)
  - 2009 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 4)
  - 2010 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 5 - 6)
  - 2011 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 7 - 8)
  - 2012 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 9)
  - 2013 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 10)
  - 2014 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 11)
  - 2015 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 12)
  - 2016 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 13)
  - 2017 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 14)
  - 2018 May 19-20 (Box Commencement 7, Folder 15)
- Convocation, 1957-1991; III
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 1)
  - 1969 Sep 11 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 2)
  - 1971 Mar 23 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 3)
    Biographical / Historical
    This convocation was in honor of U Thant
  - 1974 May 06 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 4-5)
    Wilde-Stein Convocation
  - 1976 - 1984 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 6)
  - 1980 - 1982 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 7)
  - 1981 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 8)
  - 1983 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 9-10)
  - 1984 - 1985 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 11)
  - 1986 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 12)
  - 1987 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 13, Box Artifacts 5)
  - 1991 (Box Convocation 1, Folder 14)
- Other Events, 1957-2018; IV
  - University Day, 1957 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 1)
  - Campus Preview, 1958 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 2)
  - Charter Day, 1959 - 1981 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 3)
  - Aron, Raymond, 1960 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 4)
  - Urban Future of Central Conn., 1960 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of University Hall, 1960 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 6)
  - Commager, Henry Steele, 1962 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 7)
  - Open House, 1963 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 8)
  - Naval Research Award, 1963 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1963 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 10)
  - Dinner for Alan Wilson, 1963 Nov 14 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 11)
  - University Day, 1963 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 12)
  - Open House, 1963 May (Box Other Events 1, Folder 13)
  - Secondary School Admin. Dinner, 1963 Oct 14 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 14)
  - New Staff List, 1964 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 15)
  - Urban Policy Conference Program, 1964 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 16 - 19)
  - Flagpole Dedication / Naval Day Celebration, 1964 (Box Other Events 1, Folder 20)
  - University Medal Milton H. Glover, 1965 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 1)
  - University of Hartford Dinner, 1965 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 2)
  - Dinner Annual University, 1965, 1967, 1968 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 3)
  - Hidden Languages of the Twentieth Century Smith, Henry Lee, Jr., 1965 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 4)
  - UN Model Assembly, 1965 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Wilson Changing Communist, 1965 March (Box Other Events 2, Folder 6)
  - Accreditation Dinner, 1965 April 4 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 7)
  - Adjunct Faculty Dinner, 1965 Jan 23 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 8)
  - University Day, 1965 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 9)
  - Groundbreaking Campus Center, 1965 May (Box Other Events 2, Folder 10)
  - Principals and Guidance Dinner, 1965 Jan 13 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 11)
  - Groundbreaking Charles A. Dana Hall, 1966 March 17 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Women's Club Spock Lecture, 1966 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Women's Club Meeting, 1966 October 10 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Women's Club Symposium, 1966 March 22 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Christmas Reception, 1966 December 11 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 16)
  - Dormitories Groundbreaking, 1966 March 29 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornerstone Charles A. Dana Hall, 1966 May 17 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 18)
  - Cornerstone Gengras Campus Center, 1966 April 12 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 19)
  - Committee of 100 - Orientation Session, 1966 December (Box Other Events 2, Folder 20)
  - Charter Day, 1966 March 13 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 21)
  - Charter Oak Ceremony, 1966 May 11 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 22)
  - Lincoln Foundation Tax Conference, 1966 October (Box Other Events 2, Folder 23)
  - Principals and Guidance Directors Dinner, 1966 March 03 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 24)
  - O'Connell Hall Dedication, 1966 October 30 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 25)
  - Physical Education Facility, 1966 August 12 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 26)
  - Hartt Opera - Theater Guild Anniversary Reception, 1966 November 11 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 27)
  - U of H Women's Association Board Meeting, 1966 October 13 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 28)
  - Special Report Meeting, 1966 November 03 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 29)
  - University Dinner, 1966 May 09 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 30)
  - House and Garden Tour, 1966 May (Box Other Events 2, Folder 31)
  - Women's Association U of H, 1966 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 32)
  - Groundbreaking - Bus Admin Building, 1966 July 07 (Box Other Events 2, Folder 33)
  - Technical Education Program, 1967 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 1)
  - Public Speakers List, 1967 - 1970 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 2)
  - Associates Reception, 1967 September 24 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 3)
  - 10th Anniversary Dinner, 1966 - 1967 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee - 10th Anniversary, 1966 - 1967 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Women's Club Membership meeting, 1967 February 20 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Women's Club Meeting, 1967 April 19 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Women's Club, 1967 October (Box Other Events 3, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Guidance Personnel, 1967 October 27 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 9)
  - Coffin Testimonial, 1967 May 14 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 10)
  - Charter Day Meeting, 1967 February 12 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor's Luncheon, 1967 November 12 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 12)
  - Parents Day, 1967 October 28 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 13)
  - Physical Education Building Cornerstone Cancelled, 1967 December 02 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 14)
  - Sports Writer's Dinner, 1967 November 29 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 15)
  - Orientation Sampler, 1967 April (Box Other Events 3, Folder 16)
  - Women's Association Book Sale & Reception, 1967 October (Box Other Events 3, Folder 17)
  - University Day, 1967 April (Box Other Events 3, Folder 18)
  - U of H Women's Association Board Meeting, 1967 June 12 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 19)
  - U of H Women's Association Luncheon, 1967 May 23 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 20)
  - Guidance Counselors and Directors, 1967 April 17 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 21)
  - U of H Women's Association Lectures Professors Klock, Behl, Lane, 1967 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 22)
  - Women's Association Meeting, 1967 March 06 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 23)
  - U of H Women's Association Meeting, 1967 January 18 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 24)
  - Gengras Campus Center Dedication, 1967 October 28 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 25)
  - Auerbach Hall Cornerstone, 1967 May 09 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 26)
  - Third Annual Conference on Communication in Government and Business Industry, 1967 May 13 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 27)
  - Homecoming and Alumni Homecoming Banquet, 1967 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Women's Club, 1968 January 23 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 29)
  - Estate Planning Reception, 1968 October 14 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 30)
  - Clinger Farewell Party, 1968 August 08 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 31)
  - Adjunct Faculty Meeting, 1968 April 05 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 32)
  - The media and the minorities conference, 1968 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 33)
  - Anniversary Dinner, 1968 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 34)
  - Orientation Freshman, 1968 September 11 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 35)
  - Orientation New Faculty and Staff, 1968 September 13 (Box Other Events 3, Folder 36)
  - Anniversary Dinner, U of H Medal, 1968 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 1)
  - Death of Martin Luther King, 1968 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 2)
  - Parents Day, 1968 October 19 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 3)
  - Hartford Art School Trustees, 1968 December 10 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 4)
  - U of H Associates, 11968 November 14 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 5)
  - Superintendents Dinner, 1968 October 30 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 6)
  - University of Hartford Womens Association Spring Lecture Series, 1968 March (Box Other Events 4, Folder 7)
  - University Medal, 1969 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial, 1969 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 9)
  - Gregory, Dick, 1969, 1975, 1979 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 10)
  - Superintendents Dinner, 1969 Oct 29 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Institute, 1969 Nov (Box Other Events 4, Folder 12)
  - Visiting Day, 1969 Nov 11 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 13)
  - Visiting Day Admissions Office, 1969 Nov 11 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 14)
  - NCATE, 1969 Nov 16 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 15)
  - Regents Meeting and Dinner, 1969 Nov 20 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 16)
  - Parent's Day, 1969 Oct 11 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 17)
  - Teacher's CORPS Banquet, 1969 Oct 28 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 18)
  - Groundbreaking, 1969 Sep 16 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 19)
  - Planning Commission, 1969 Sep 20-21 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 20)
  - Small Business Conference, 1969 Jun (Box Other Events 4, Folder 21)
  - Brazilian Mayors, 1969 Sep 04 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 22)
  - Adjunct Faculty Annual Meeting, 1969 Sep 8 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 23)
  - Staff Reception, 1969 May 20 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 24)
  - Moore and Salsbury Unveiling of Statuary IN Honor of Chas. SalsBury, 1969 May 22 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 25)
  - Planning Commission Weekend Northfield Inn, 1969 Mar (Box Other Events 4, Folder 26)
  - U of H Medal Luncheon, 1969 Apr 29 (Box Other Events 4, Folder 27)
  - Charter Day, 1969 Feb (Box Other Events 5, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee on Education, 1969 Apr 24 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 2)
  - Groundbreaking Library, 1969 Sep 16 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 3)
  - Black American's Speak Through the Arts, 1970 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 4)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1970 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 5)
  - Hartt 50th Anniversary, 1970 Apr 17 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 6)
  - After Theater Party Russell House, 1970 Dec 18 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 7)
  - Chancellor's Commencement Luncheon, 1970 Jun 07 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 8)
  - Ward Groundbreaking, 1970 Aug 26 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 9)
  - Isaac Stern Degree Conferral, 1971 Apr 25 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 10)
  - Project Inquire, 1970 Nov 30 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 11)
  - Business School Reception, 1970 Oct 23 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 12)
  - Charles Avila Luncheon, 1970 Sep 22 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 13)
  - Estate Planners, 1970 Apr - May (Box Other Events 5, Folder 14)
  - Art School Reception, 1970 Apr 23 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council Meeting, 1970 Apr 09 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 16)
  - Accreditation Guests, 1970 April 05 - 07 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors - Associates, 1970 Dec 08 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 18)
  - Deans Annual Dinner, 1970 Mar 13 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 19)
  - Art School Dinner, 1970 Feb 27 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 20)
  - Regents Luncheon Meeting, 1970 May 05 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 21)
  - Basketball Dinner, 1970 Apr 29 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 22)
  - Wilson Honorary Event, 1970 May 20 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 23)
  - Project Support, 1971 Jan 21 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 24)
  - Dinner for the Archbishop, 1971 Feb 04 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 25)
  - Regents Luncheon Meeting, 1971 Feb 17 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 26)
  - New Regents Luncheon, 1971 Jan 14 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 27)
  - Library Dedication Lists, 1971 Oct 03 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 28)
  - Library Dedication Program, 1971 Oct 03 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 29)
  - Development Staff Meeting, 1971 Jun 08 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 30)
  - Enlightenment Society Dinner, 1971 Oct 27 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 31)
  - Hartt Opera Guild Event, 1971 Nov 27 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 32)
  - Hard Hat Party, 1971 Aug 21 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 33)
  - Coffin Plaque Ceremony, 1971 Sep 24 (Box Other Events 5, Folder 34)
  - Women's Association Pop Concert, 1971 May 21 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 1)
  - Art School Trustees Luncheons Dates, 1971 May 26 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 2)
  - O'Connell-Fuller Dinner, 1971 May 27 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 3)
  - Parents Day, 1971 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 4)
  - Dinner for Mayor Athanson, 1971 Jun 07 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 5)
  - Muskie/Edmund, 1971 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 6)
  - Parents Day, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 7)
  - Basketball Dinner, 1972 Apr 20 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 8)
  - "China in Perspective", 1972 May (Box Other Events 6, Folder 9)
  - Estate Planning, 1972 Mar 27 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 10)
  - Rostropovich Ceremony, 1972 Feb 01 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 11)
  - Associates Open House, 1972 May 25 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 12)
  - Ward East Hall Dedication, 1972 Apr 30 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 13)
  - Associates - Cagenello Event, 1972 Jun 28 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 14)
  - Kilbourn-Ward Medal Ceremony, 1972 May 23 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 15)
  - Lou Sampliner Honorary Degree, 1972 May 09 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 16)
  - Yung Wing Memorial Ceremony, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 17)
  - Yung Wing Ceremony - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 18)
  - Yung Wing Ceremony - Publicity, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 19)
  - Yung Wing Ceremony, 1972 Aug 26 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 20)
  - Lescarbeau Memorial Service, 1972 Nov 11 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 21)
  - Hartford Courant Article by Don Noel Campus Tour, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 22)
  - Space Awards Ceremony, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 23)
  - Tennessee Williams / Honorary Degree, 1972 (Box Other Events 6, Folder 24)
  - Parents Day - Arrangements, 1973 Oct 27 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 1)
  - Beatman - Perlman Publicity, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 2)
  - Beatman Lectures - Correspondence, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 3)
  - Beatman - Perlman Arrangements, 1973 Nov 20 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 4)
  - Beatman Financial, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 5)
  - Beatman Community Program, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 6)
  - Pearlman, Iztack, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 7)
  - Beatman Community Program / Wicker, Tom, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 8)
  - Nixon - Kissinger Foreign Policy, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 9)
  - Wicker, Tom / New York Times / Watergate, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 10)
  - Beatman Lecture Tom Wicker, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 11)
  - Beatman - Perlman Lists, 1973 Nov 20 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 12)